Guide to the Stanford University, Press, Archival Book Copies
Stanford University. Libraries.
- 2007
  - Selfridge-Field, Eleanor, Song and Season: Science, Culture, and Theatrical Time in Early Modern Venice., 2007 (Box 11)
  - Selfridge-Field, Eleanor, The Calendar of Venetian Opera: A New Chronology of Venetian Opera and Related Genres, 1660-1760., 2007 (Box 12)
  - Shavit, Yossi, Richard Arum, and Adam Gamoran, ed, Stratification in Higher Education., 2007 (Box 12)
  - Shreiber, Maeera Y, Singing in a Strange Land: A Jewish American Poetics., 2007 (Box 12)
  - Soares, Joseph A, The Power of Privilege: Yale and America's Elite Colleges., 2007 (Box 12)
  - Sorensen, Diana, A Turbulent Decade Remembered., 2007 (Box 12)
  - Steinberg, Stephen, Race Relations: A Critiquen., 2007 (Box 12)
  - Strach, Patricia, All in the Family: The Private Roots of American Public Policy., 2007 (Box 12)
  - Svallfors, Stefan, ed, The Political Sociology of the Welfare State., 2007 (Box 12)
  - Swedberg, Nee, On Capitalism., 2007 (Box 12)
  - Szafraniec, Asja, Beckett, Derrida, and the Event of Literature., 2007 (Box 13)
  - Tabrizi, Behnam N. and Mitchell M. Tseng, Transformation Through Global Value Chains: Taking Advantage of Business Synergies in the United States and China., 2007 (Box 13)
  - Tarn, Nathaniel, The Embattled Lyric., 2007 (Box 13)
  - Thomson, Alex, A Glossary of U. S. Politics and Government., 2007 (Box 13)
  - Tsadik, Daniel, Between Foreigners and Shi'is: Nineteenth Century Iran and Its Jewish Minority., 2007 (Box 13)
  - Turam, Berna, Between Islam and the State- The Politics of Engagement., 2007 (Box 13)
  - U, Eddy, Disorganizing China: Counter-Bureaucracy and the Decline of Socialism., 2007 (Box 13)
  - Ueda, Atsuko, Concealment of Politics, Politics of Concealment: The Production of "Literature" in Meiji Japan., 2007 (Box 13)
  - van Dijck, Jose, Mediated Memories in the Digital Age., 2007 (Box 13)
  - Venkatesch, Sudhir Alladi, Youth, Globalization and the Law., 2007 (Box 13)
  - Vitalis, Robert, America's Kingdom- Mythmaking on the Saudi Oil Frontier., 2007 (Box 13)
  - Wachman, Alan M, Why Taiwan? Geostrategic Rationales for China's Territorial Integrity., 2007 (Box 13)
  - Wells, Marion A, The Secret Wound; Love-Melancholy and Early Modern Romance., 2007 (Box 14)
  - Willer, David and Henry A. Walker, Building Experiments., 2007 (Box 14)
  - Williams, John Alexander, Turning to Nature in Germany: Hiking, Nudism, and Conservation, 1900-1940., 2007 (Box 14)
  - Wolff, Larry and Marco Cipolloni, ed, The Anthropology of the Enlightenment., 2007 (Box 14)
  - Zabus, Chantal, Between Rites and Rights: Excision in Women's Experimental Texts and Human Contexts., 2007 (Box 14)
  - Zaller, Robert, The Discourse of Legitimacy in Early Modern Europe., 2007 (Box 14)
- 2008
  - Adams, Thomas K, The Army after next; the first postindustrial army., 2008 (Box 1)
  - Alagappa, Muthiah, ed, The long shadow; nuclear weapons and security in 21st century Asia., 2008 (Box 1)
  - Aldrich, Howard E, Organizations and Environments., 2008 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Terry L., Laura E. Huggins, and Thomas Michael Power, Accounting for Mother Nature: Changing Demands for her Bounty., 2008 (Box 1)
  - Anidjar, Gil, Semites: Race, Religion, Literature., 2008 (Box 1)
  - Baptandier, Brigitte, The lady of Linshui; a Chinese female cult., 2008 (Box 1)
  - Barnes, Thomas Garden, Shaping the Common Law., 2008 (Box 1)
  - Baxstrom, Richard, Houses in Motion; the experience of place and the problem of belief in urban Malaysia., 2008 (Box 1)
  - Beamish, Anne, Learning from Work., 2008 (Box 1)
  - Benei, Veronique, Schooling Passions., 2008 (Box 1)
  - Bernstein, Susan, Housing problems; writing and architecture in Goethe..., 2008 (Box 1)
  - Birnbaum, Pierre, Geography of Hope: Exile, the Enlightenment, Disassimiliation., 2008 (Box 2)
  - Bortz, Jeffrey, Revolution with the Revolution; cotton textile workers..., 2008 (Box 2)
  - Bronstein, Jamie L, Caught in the Machinery: Workplace Accidents and Injured Workers in 19th Century Britain., 2008 (Box 2)
  - Camden, Vera J, Trauma and Transformation: The Political Progress of John Bunyan., 2008 (Box 2)
  - Carnochan, W. B, Golden Legends; images of Abyssinia, Samuel Johnson to Bob Marley., 2008 (Box 2)
  - Cassidy, Robert M, Counterinsurgency and the Global War on Terror: Military Culture and the Irregular War., 2008 (Box 2)
  - Chan, Jennifer, Another Japan Is Possible., 2008 (Box 2)
  - Chander, Anupam, et. al, Securing Privacy in the Internet Age., 2008 (Box 2)
  - Chang, Gordon, et. al., eds, Asian American Art, a History, 1850-1970., 2008 (Box 2)
  - Chavez, Leo R, The Latino Threat; constructing immigrants, citizens, and the nation., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Chemerinsky, Erwin, Enhancing Government; Federalism for the 21st Century., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Chernus, Ira, Apocalypse Management: Eisenhower and the Discourse of National Insecurity., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Clunan, Anne L., ed, Terrorism, War, or Disease?., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Conklin, William E, Hegel's Laws; the legitimacy of a modern legal order., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Cordesman, Anthony H, Arab-Israeli Military Forces in an Era of Asymmetric Wars., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Coyne, Christopher J, After War: The Political Economy of Exploiting Democracy., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Culbert, Jennifer, Dead Certainty: The Death Penalty and the Problem of Judgment., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Culbert, Samuel A, Beyond Bullsh*t: Straight-Talk At Work., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Davis, Richard W, A Political History of the House of Lords, 1811-1846., 2008 (Box 3)
  - De Been, Wouter, Legal Realism Regained: Saaving Realism from Critical Acclaim., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Delaporte, Francois, Anatomy of the Passions., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Derrida, Jacques, Psyche: Inventions of the Order, Volume II., 2008 (Box 3)
  - Detienne, Marcel, Comparing the incomparable., 2008 (Box 4)
  - Diamond, John, The CIA and the culture of failure., 2008 (Box 4)
  - Dillon, Nara and Jean C. Oi, At the Crossroads of Empires: Middlemen., 2008 (Box 4)
  - Dubber, Markus D., ed, Police and the Liberal State., 2008 (Box 4)
  - Dudas, Jeffrey R, The Cultivation of Resentment., 2008 (Box 4)
  - Duffield, John S, Over a Barrel: The Costs of US Foreign Oil Dependence., 2008 (Box 4)
  - Edwards, Louise, Gender, Politics, and Democracy: Women's Suffrage in China., 2008 (Box 4)
  - Eley, Geoff and Jan Palmowski, Citizenship and National Identity in 20th Century Germany., 2008 (Box 4)
  - Elkins, James, Six Stories from the End of Representation: Images in Painting, Photography, Astronomy, Microscopy, Particle Physics, and Quantum Mechanics, 1980-2000., 2008 (Box 4)
  - Ellenzweig, Sarah, The Fringes of Belief., 2008 (Box 4)
  - Eskin, Michael, Poetic Affairs: Celan, Grunbein, Brodsky., 2008 (Box 4)
  - Ewing, Katherine Pratt, Stolen Honor; stigmatizing Muslim men in Berlin., 2008 (Box 5)
  - Ferry, Anne, By design; intention in poetry., 2008 (Box 5)
  - Fidler, David P. and Lawrence O. Gostin, Biosecurity in the Global Age: Biological Weapons, Public Health, and the Rule of Law., 2008 (Box 5)
  - Fina, Siegfried, ed, European Union E-Commerce Law., 2008 (Box 5)
  - Fischer, Brodwyn, A Poverty of Rights., 2008 (Box 5)
  - Francois, Anne-Lise, Open Secrets: The Literature of Uncounted Experience., 2008 (Box 5)
  - Frost, Samantha, Lessons from a Materialist Thinker., 2008 (Box 5)
  - Gans, Eric, The Scenic Imagination: Originary Thinking from Hobbes to the Present Day., 2008 (Box 5)
  - Girard, Rene, Mimesis and theory; essays on literature and criticism, 1953-2005., 2008 (Box 5)
  - Goldberg, Steven, Bleached Faith: The Tragic Cost When Religion is Forced Into the Public Square., 2008 (Box 5)
  - Goode, Erich, ed, Out of control; assessing the general theory of crime., 2008 (Box 5)
  - Guseva, Alya, Into the Red; the birth of the credit card market ..., 2008 (Box 5)
  - Haber, Stephen, Douglass C. North, and Barry R. Weingast, Political Institutions and Financial Development., 2008 (Box 6)
  - Hagglund, Martin, Radical atheism; Derrida and the time of life., 2008 (Box 6)
  - Hale, Charles A, Emilio Rabasa and the survival of Porfirian liberalism., 2008 (Box 6)
  - Hanser, Amy, Service Encounters: Class, Gender, and the Market for Social Distinction in Urban China., 2008` (Box 6)
  - Herold, David M, Change the way you lead change; leadership strategies that really work., 2008 (Box 6)
  - Hollander, Dana, Exemplarity and Chosenness; Rosenzweig and Derrida..., 2008 (Box 6)
  - Hoyk, Robert, The ethical executive., 2008 (Box 6)
  - Hull, Christopher C, Grassroots Rules: How the Iowa Caucus Helps Elect American Presidents., 2008 (Box 6)
  - Ito, Ken K, An age of melodrama; family, gender and social hierarchy in the turn-of-the-century Japanese novel., 2008 (Box 6)
  - Jackson, Leon, The Business of Letters: Authorial Economies in Antebellum America., 2008 (Box 6)
  - Jacobs, Carol, Skirting the Ethical., 2008 (Box 6)
  - Jeffery, Craig and Patricia Jeffery and Roger Jeffery, Degrees Without Freedom? Education, Masculinities, and Unemployment in North India., 2008 (Box 6)
  - Judge, Joan, The Precious Raft of History: The Past, the West, and the Woman Question in China., 2008 (Box 6)
  - Khanna, Ranjanna, Algeria Cuts: Women & Representatives, 1830 to the Present., 2008 (Box 7)
  - Khazzoom, Aziza, Shifting Ethnic Boudnaries and Inequality in Israel: Or, How the Polish Peddler Became a German Intellectual., 2008 (Box 7)
  - Kim, Nadia Y, Imperial citizens; Koreans and race from Seoul to LA., 2008 (Box 7)
  - Kimura, Hiroshi, The Kurillian knot; a history of Japanese-Russian border negotiations., 2008 (Box 7)
  - Kottman, Paul A, A Politics of the Scene., 2008 (Box 7)
  - Krasny, Michael, Off Mike: A Memoir of Talk Radio and Literary Life., 2008 (Box 7)
  - Kuhonta, Erik Martinez, ed, Southeast Asia in Political Science., 2008 (Box 7)
  - Laszlo, Chris, Sustainable Value: How the World's Leading Companies are Doing Well by Doing Good., 2008 (Box 7)
  - Lavrin, Asuncion, Brides of Christ; conventual life in colonial Mexico., 2008 (Box 7)
  - Lee, Yong Wook, The Japanese Challenge to the American Neoliberal World Order., 2008 (Box 7)
  - Lefebvre, Alexandre, The image of law; Deleuze, Bergson, Spinoza., 2008 (Box 7)
  - Lu, Weijing, True to Her Word: The Faithful Maiden Cult in Late Imperial China., 2008 (Box 8)
  - MacCormick, Neil, H.L.A. Hart, second edition., 2008 (Box 8)
  - Macdonald, Iain and Krzysztof Ziarek, Adorno and Heidegger: Philosophical Questions., 2008 (Box 8)
  - March, James G, Explorations in organizations., 2008 (Box 8)
  - Martin, Isaac William, The Permanent Tax Revolt: How the Property Tax Transformed American Politics., 2008 (Box 8)
  - Martinez, Maria Elena, Genealogical Fictions; Limpieze de sangre, religion, and gender in colonial Mexico., 2008 (Box 8)
  - McAllister, Lesley K, Making Law Matter., 2008 (Box 8)
  - McGrath, Jason, Postsocialist Modernity: Chinese Cinema, Literature, and Criticism in the Market Age., 2008 (Box 8)
  - Menke, Richard, Telegraphic Realism: Victorian Fiction and Other Information Systems., 2008 (Box 8)
  - Miceli, Thomas J, The Conomic Approach to Law; 2nd edition., 2008 (Box 8)
  - Miskel, James F, Disaster Response and Homeland Security: What Works, What Doesn't., 2008 (Box 8)
  - Mockaitis, Thomas R, The "New" terrorism; myths and reality., 2008 (Box 8)
  - Moghalu, Chiedu Kingsley, Global Justice: The Politics of War Crimes Trials., 2008 (Box 8)
  - Moltz, James Clay, The Politics of Space Security., 2008 (Box 9)
  - Morrissey, Lee, The Constitution of Literature: Literacy, Democracy, and Early English Literary Criticism., 2008 (Box 9)
  - Murray, Alice Yang, Historical Memories of the Japanese American Internment and the Struggle for Redress., 2008 (Box 9)
  - Nadav, Mordechai, The Jews of Pinsk, 1506 to 1880., 2008 (Box 9)
  - Nancy, Jean-Luc, The Discourse of the Syncope: Logodaedalus., 2008 (Box 9)
  - Nealon, Jeffrey T, Foucault beyond Foucault., 2008 (Box 9)
  - Newendorp, Nicole Dejong, Uneasy reunions; immigration, citizenship and family life in post-1997 Hong Kong., 2008 (Box 9)
  - Oros, Andrew L, Normalizing Japan., 2008 (Box 9)
  - Owensby, Brian P, Empire of Law and Indian Justice in Colonial Mexico., 2008 (Box 9)
  - Patico, Jennifer, Consumption and Social Change in a Post-Soviet middle class., 2008 (Box 9)
  - Peeren, Esther, Intersubjectivities and Popular Culture: Bakhtin and Beyond., 2008 (Box 10)
  - Pekkanen, Saadia M, Japan's Aggressive Legalism., 2008 (Box 10)
  - Peretz, Eyal, Becoming Visionary: Brian de Palma's Cinematic Education of the Sense., 2008 (Box 10)
  - Perpich, Diane, The Ethics of Emmanuel Levinas., 2008 (Box 10)
  - Phillips, James, ed, Cinematic thinking; philosophical approaches to the new cinema., 2008 (Box 10)
  - Pinaire, Brian K, The Constitution of Electoral Speech Law: The Supreme Court and Freedom of Expression in Campaigns and Elections., 2008 (Box 10)
  - Powell, Benjamin, Making Poor Nations Rich: Entrepreneurship and the Process of Economic Deveolopment., 2008 (Box 10)
  - Proctor, Robert N., ed, Agnotology; the making and unmaking of ignorance., 2008 (Box 10)
  - Ramirez-Christensen, Esperanza, Emptiness and Temporality., 2008 (Box 10)
  - Ramirez-Christensen, Esperanza, Murmured Conversations., 2008 (Box 10)
  - Ramsay, Jacob, Mandarins and Martyrs; the Church and the Nguyen Dynasty ..., 2008 (Box 10)
  - Razo, Armando, Social Foundations of Limited Dictatorship: Networks and Private Protection During Mexico's Early Industrialization., 2008 (Box 10)
  - Rein, Raanan, In the Shadow of Peron., 2008 (Box 11)
  - Resina, Joan Ramon, Barcelona's vocation of modernity., 2008 (Box 11)
  - Ricklefs, M. C, A History of Modern Indonesia scine c. 1200; 4th ed., 2008 (Box 11)
  - Ristaino, Marcia R, The Jacquinot Safe Zone: Wartime Refugees in Shanghai., 2008 (Box 11)
  - Ro'i, Yaacov, ed, The Soviet Union and the June 1967 Six Day War., 2008 (Box 11)
  - Roe, Emery, High reliability management; operating on the edge., 2008 (Box 11)
  - Rosenshield, Gary, The ridiculous Jew; the exploitation and transformation..., 2008 (Box 11)
  - Ross, Stephen F, Fans of the world unite!., 2008 (Box 11)
  - Rubin, Ronald, Silencing the demon's advocate; the strategy of Descartes' Meditations., 2008 (Box 11)
  - Sarlo, Beatriz, The Technical Imagination., 2008 (Box 11)
  - Scheffler, Richard M, Is there a doctor in the house? market signals and tomorrow's supply of doctors., 2008 (Box 11)
  - Schiebinger, Londa, Gendered Innovations in Science and Engineering., 2008 (Box 11)
  - Schwartz, Regina Mara, Sacramental poetics at the dawn of secularism., 2008 (Box 11)
  - Selznick, Philip, A Humanist science; values and ideals in social inquiry., 2008 (Box 12)
  - Simpson, Bradley R, Economists with guns; authoritarian develoment and U.S.-Indonesian relations, 1960-1968., 2008 (Box 12)
  - Sklansky, David Alan, Democracy and the Police., 2008 (Box 12)
  - Speed, Shannon, Rights in Rebellion: Indigenous Struggle and Human Rights in Chiapas., 2008 (Box 12)
  - Tang, Chenxi, The Geographic Imagination of Modernity., 2008 (Box 12)
  - Taylor, matthew P, Judging Policy: Courts and Policy Reform in Democratic Brazil., 2008 (Box 12)
  - Tepe, Sultan, Beyond Sacred and Secular; politics of religion in Israel and Turkey., 2008 (Box 12)
  - Torlasco, Domietta, The time of the crime; phenomenology, psychoanalysis, Italian film., 2008 (Box 12)
  - Tsang, Steve, ed, Intelligence and Human Rights in the Era of Global Terrorism., 2008 (Box 12)
  - Ulloa, Marie-Pierre, Francis Jeanson; a dissident intellectual from the French resistance to the Algerian War., 2008 (Box 12)
  - Vismann, Cornelia, Files; law and media technology., 2008 (Box 12)
  - Wang, Di, The teahouse; small business, everyday culture, and public politics in Chengdu, 1900-1950., 2008 (Box 12)
  - Wang, Feng, Boundaries and Categories: Rising Inequality in Post-Socialist Urban China., 2008 (Box 13)
  - Weber, Thomas, Our Friend "The Enemy:" Elite Education in Britain and Germany Before World War I., 2008 (Box 13)
  - Xu, Xiaoqun, Trial of Modernity; judical reform in early 20th century China., 2008 (Box 13)
  - Zhang, Sheldon X, Chinese Human Smuggling Organizations: Families, Social Networks, and Cultural Imperatives., 2008 (Box 13)
  - Zheng, Yongnian, Technological Empowerment: The Internet, State, and Society in China., 2008 (Box 13)
- 2009
  - Agamben, Giorgio, What is an apparatus? and other essays., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Alacevich, Michele, The political economy of the World Bank, the early years., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Andreas, Joel, Rise of the red engineers; the cultural revolution and the origins of China's new class., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Ankersmit, Frank, ed, Re-figuring Hayden White., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Ashiwa, Yoshiko and David L. Wank, eds, Making religion, making the state: the politics of religion in modern China., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Aspinall, Edward, Islam and nation: separatist rebellion in Aceh, Indonesia., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Ba, Alice D, [Re]Negotiating East and Southeast Asia., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Bailey, Stanley R, Legacies of race; identities, attitudes, and politics in Brazil., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Bair, Jennifer, ed, Frontiers of Commodity Chain Research., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Bajorek, Jennifer, Counterfeit Capital; poetic labor and revolutionary iry., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Barbieri, Magali and Daniele Belanger eds, Reconfiguring families in contemporary Vietnam., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Barlow, Jeffrey G, From Hot War to Cold: the U.S. Navy and National Security Affairs, 1945-1955., 2009 (Box 1)
  - Barrass, Gordon S, The Great Cold War., 2009 (Box 2)
  - Bashkin, Orit, The Other Iraq; pluralism and culture in Hasemite Irag., 2009 (Box 2)
  - Bays, Daniel H. and Ellen Widmer, eds, China's Christian colleges; cross-cultural connections, 1900-1950., 2009 (Box 2)
  - Befort, Stephen F. and John W. Budd, Invisible Hands, Invisible Objectives., 2009 (Box 2)
  - Behrens, Alfredo, Culture and management in the Americas., 2009 (Box 2)
  - Bergelson, Vera, Victims' rights and victims' wrongs., 2009 (Box 2)
  - Bergere, Marie-Claire, Shanghai: China's Gateway to Modernity., 2009 (Box 2)
  - Biemann, Asher D, Inventing New Beginnings., 2009 (Box 2)
  - Blauner, Bob, Resisting McCarthyism: to sign or not to sign California's loyalty oath., 2009 (Box 2)
  - Bleichman, Daniela, et. al, Science in the Spanish and Portuguese Empires 1500-1800., 2009 (Box 2)
  - Boutilier, Robert, Stakeholder Politics., 2009 (Box 3)
  - Bowman, Steven B, The Agony of Greek Jews, 1940-1945., 2009 (Box 3)
  - Bowman, Steven B, The Agony of Greek Jews, 1940-1945., 2009 (Box 15)
  - Case, Holly, Between states: the Transylvanian question and the European idea during World War II., 2009 (Box 3)
  - Chalcraft, John, The Invisible Cage; Syrian migrant workers in Lebanon., 2009 (Box 3)
  - Chu, Hsiao-Yun and Roberto G. Trujillo, eds, New views on R. Buckminster Fuller., 2009 (Box 3)
  - Clarke, Sally H., et. al., eds, The challenge of remaining innovative., 2009 (Box 3)
  - Coopan, Vilashini, Worlds Within., 2009 (Box 3)
  - Cross, Frank B, The Theory and Practice of Statutory Interpretation., 2009 (Box 3)
  - Crowther, Paul, Phenomenology of the Visual Arts (even the frame)., 2009 (Box 3)
  - Davis, Deborah S. and Wang Feng, eds, Creating Wealth and Poverty in Postsocialist China., 2009 (Box 3)
  - De la Durantaye, Leland, Giorgio Agamben, a critical introduction., 2009 (Box 3)
  - Diener, Alexander C, One homland or two?: the nationalization and transnationalization of Mongolia's Kazakhs., 2009 (Box 4)
  - Drake, Paul W., Between Tyranny and Anarchy., 2009 (Box 4)
  - Duffield, John S., ed, Balance Sheet: the Iraq war and U. S. national security., 2009 (Box 4)
  - Elfenbein, Andrew, Romanticism and the Rise of English., 2009 (Box 4)
  - Engel, David M. and Michael McCann, eds, Fault lines: tort law as cultural practice., 2009 (Box 4)
  - Enyeart, John P, The quest for "just and pure law"; Rocky Mountian workers and American social democarcy, 1870-1924., 2009 (Box 4)
  - Findlen, Paula, et. al., eds, Italy's Eighteenth Century., 2009 (Box 4)
  - Fishbane, Eitan P, As light before dawn; the inner world of a Medieval Kabbalist., 2009 (Box 4)
  - Flanigan, James, Smith Southern California, You're the Center of the Universe., 2009 (Box 4)
  - Fleming, Paul, Exemplarity and Mediocrity; the art of the average from bourgeois tragedy to realism., 2009 (Box 4)
  - Flowers, Petrice R, Refugees, Women and Weapons., 2009 (Box 4)
  - Franke, William, Poetry and Apocalypse; theological disclosures of poetic language., 2009 (Box 5)
  - Freeman, Kirrily, Bronzes to Bullets; Vicy and the destruction of French public statuary, 1941-1944., 2009 (Box 5)
  - Freidin, Gregory, ed, The Enigma of Isaac Babel., 2009 (Box 5)
  - Friedman, Lawrence M, Dead hands; a social history of wills, trusts, and inheritance law., 2009 (Box 5)
  - Fruchtl, Josef, The Impertinent Self; a Heroic History of Modernity., 2009 (Box 5)
  - Garcia Duttmann, Alexander, Visconti, Insights into Flesh and Blood., 2009 (Box 5)
  - Gasche, Rudolphe, Europe, or the Infinite Task., 2009 (Box 5)
  - Gasper, Michael Ezekiel, The Power of Representation; publics, peasants & Island in Egypt., 2009 (Box 5)
  - Gillerman, Sharon, Germans into Jews; remaking the Jewish social body in the Weimar Republic., 2009 (Box 5)
  - Gilmore, Paul, Aesthetic Materialism., 2009 (Box 5)
  - Glenn, Evelyn Nakano, ed, Shades of Difference: Why Skin Color Matters., 2009 (Box 5)
  - Goldman, Alan, Transforming Toxic Leaders., 2009 (Box 5)
  - Goodale, Mark, Dilemmas of Modernity; Bolivian encounters with law and liberalism., 2009 (Box 5)
  - Goodale, Mark, Surrendering to Utopia; an anthropology of human rights., 2009 (Box 6)
  - Goscha, Christopher E., ed, Connecting Histories; Decolonization and the Cold War in Southeast Asia, 1945-1962., 2009 (Box 6)
  - Graham, Thomas, Jr, Preventing catastrophe., 2009 (Box 6)
  - Greene, Shane, Customizing Indigeneity; paths to a visionary politics in Peru., 2009 (Box 6)
  - Gregor, A. James, Marxism, Fascism, and Totalitarianism., 2009 (Box 6)
  - Gregory, Neil, et. al, New industries from new places., 2009 (Box 6)
  - Hadot, Pierre, The Present Alone is Our Happiness; conversations with Jeannie Carlier and Arnold I. Davidson., 2009 (Box 6)
  - Haj, Samira, Reconfiguring Islamic Tradition., 2009 (Box 6)
  - Halliday, Terence C. and Bruce G. Carruthers, Bankrupt: global lawmaking and systemic financial crisis., 2009 (Box 6)
  - Halsall, Francis, et. al, Rediscovering Aesthetics., 2009 (Box 6)
  - Han, Hahrie, Moved to action; motivation, participation, and inequality in American politics., 2009 (Box 6)
  - Harrington, Brooke, ed, Deception; from ancient empires to Internet dating., 2009 (Box 7)
  - Hayes, Julie Candler, Translation, Subjectivity and Culture in France and England, 1600-1800., 2009 (Box 7)
  - Hechter, Michael and Christine Horne, eds, Theories of social order; a reader. Second edition., 2009 (Box 7)
  - Hellner-Eshed, Melila, A River flows from Eden; the language of mystical experience in the Zohar., 2009 (Box 7)
  - Hertog, Ekaterina, Tough choices; bearing an illegitimate child in Japan., 2009 (Box 7)
  - Hess, Julia Meredith, Immigrant Ambassadors; citizenship and belonging in the Tibetan diaspora., 2009 (Box 7)
  - Hinton, Deveon E. and Byron J. Good, eds, Culture and Panic Disorder., 2009 (Box 7)
  - Horne, Christine, The rewards of punishment; a relational theory of norm enforcement., 2009 (Box 7)
  - House, Charles H, The HP Phenomenon., 2009 (Box 7)
  - Hua, Shiping, Chinese Utopianism., 2009 (Box 7)
  - Imber, Colin, Ebu's-Su'ud: the Islamic legal Tradition., 2009 (Box 7)
  - Jansen, Jonathan D, Knowledge in the blood; confronting race and the Apartheid past., 2009 (Box 8)
  - Jeffers, Robinson, The collected letters of Robinson Jeffers; volume one., 2009 (Box 8)